[Music]
Hey, give me a
car,
you should
check the hotel quickly
[laughter]
[music]
[music] If it's a
year or a day,
everyone should go to Bhubaneshwar
Hey, the road is
empty, hey,
look,
hey, the
whole
auto [
music] Look, the road is also full, the
car is running,
go to the capital, see the condition of the capital, hey ...
Call the car, hey call
brother, the car is not running, look, it's the engineer
auto, a
two brother, look, the Rajdhani road is completely missing,
look, go and see the
water, hey
brother, we are
life, hey,
boundary and water too,
hey Baba, hurry up, hey
straight,
hey Maulana Mauchhala wala [
laughter], hey
such a face, get it filtered [music] [music]
hey Chhanna Chhanna [laughter] [music] [music] [
music] [music]
Jai
everyone, listen to the relief wala, the relief wala [music] the
relief is
also
heavy
[laughter]
who is the normal filtered
Dhil
brother, hey hey hey hey hey hey what will I earn
[music]
brother, hey
[laughter]
brother, I saw the delivery, the delivery and dedication,
first of all, I am
praised, I will
come and give you a
lift, Roha, no
helmet, no seat belt, show your license, hey,
two wheeler helmet, four wheeler seat
belt
[music]
hurry up
Baba [laughter] come [
music]
Hey Bhuvan,
hey, I
saw the TV, Bhuvan saw the water park, the
entire Bhubaneshwar,
see the people of the water park, no one
[laughter]
[music]